Hey, you.
What do you think of me?
You're totally charming.
Who in our major
doesn't like Yoo Chae-min?
If they don't, they're
the one with the problem.
Right, Min-seo?
[Episode 3]
[Tell Me Your Wish]
But why does
that person dislike me?
I don't like him.
Why?
He seemed like
a good person to me.
I don't trust faces
I trust actions.
What did he do to you?
Maybe he's planning to?
Han Se-woon!
I got it while I was as it.
This is really tasty.
How did he know
I have a peanut allergy?
Did he snoop on
my social media already?
Since it's mine
I can do what I want, right?
I waited in line for
an hour to get that.
That's not all.
You saw it too, right?
Cafeteria.
Café.
Good job, everyone.
He even followed me
to my club room.
I'm sure
Han Se-woon.
He's trying to
find something out.
Even if we bump into each
other a few times by chance
he never even says hi.
It's really getting
on my nerves.
I became the club president
because of him.